vivmag.com 2014-02-11

# Privacy Policy | Womens Digital Online Magazine | VIVMag

_Last Updated March 16, 2012_

VIV Publishing, LLC (“VIV”) owns and operates the _VIVmag_ website. _VIVmag_ committed to protecting its users’ privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to personally identifiable information we collect on the _VIVmag_ website located at [www.vivmag.com](http://www.vivmag.com/) (the “Site”). Your use of the Site is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand how we treat information collected on this Site. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

**Information We Collect**

Although the Site is available without registration, in order to take advantage of some of our Site’s features, you will be asked to provide personal information. This personal information will be collected at various pages on the Site, such as the subscription page and pages that allow registration for various services including: viewing the digital magazine; surveys, contests or promotional events; email newsletters; and VIV MOMENTS and other forum and networking sites, should they become available.

Personal information collected on these pages may include your first and last name, email address, phone number, address and other similar information. Providing this information is optional, but failure to do so in some cases will limit the services available to you. In addition, you may choose to provide VIVmag with personal information if you contact us by email.

_VIVmag‘s_ web servers automatically collect Site usage information from you when you visit the Site, such as IP addresses, browser types, operating systems, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses. Site usage information informs us about how our visitors use and navigate the Site. In addition, certain pages of the Site may use cookies to track and store your information for the purposes described in this policy. Cookies are small files that are placed on your hard disk to allow us to recognize you if you return to the Site using the same computer and browser. _VIVmag_ does not store any of your personal information in cookies. A cookie cannot read any other data off your hard drive, pass on a virus, or read cookie files created by other websites. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. While you may decide not to accept cookies, by doing so, you may not be able to experience the full functionality of our Site.

**How We Use Your Information**

We may combine the personally identifiable information you provide _VIVmag_ with other information about you that is available to us, including information from third parties. _VIVmag_ does not rent, sell, or trade any personally identifiable information but may use your information to, among other things:

  * deliver newsletters
  * service your account and customer support requests
  * notify you of special offers or promotions
  * respond to your inquiries
  * compile anonymous, aggregated information that is useful to develop new features, improve the content and navigation of the Site, analyze trends and statistics, and ensure our Site remains relevant to your needs
  * enforce _VIVmag‘s_ Terms of Use and otherwise prevent illegal or improper activity related to the Site
  * notify you of changes to this Privacy Policy or to other policies or terms that may affect you and your use of the Site
  * create user profiles

For the purposes described above, we may share your information with third party service providers, such as website operators, providers of complimentary complementary services, marketing companies and, where appropriate, law enforcement authorities. In addition, _VIVmag_ may process and fulfill magazine subscriptions through third party service providers. Whenever _VIVmag_ shares your information with third parties, those third parties are obligated (except where otherwise required by law enforcement authorities) to treat your personally identifiable information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We may also disclose your information in connection with any merger or consolidation with, or sale of all or substantially all of our assets to a third party, provided that such third party agrees to comply with our Privacy Policy. In the event _VIVmag_ sells its assets, including its database, your personal information will be transferred to the purchaser.

**Security**

_VIVmag_ maintains commercially reasonable safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personally identifiable information submitted to our Site, and we periodically review and update security measures in light of current technologies. Your password is a component of the _VIVmag_ security system. As such, it is your responsibility to protect it. Do not share your password with any third parties. If your password has been compromised for any reason, you should notify _[VIVmag](http://vivmag.com/contact-us/)_ immediately. 

**Your Ability to Choose**

We communicate with you to provide you information that you have requested. We will also send you valuable information and offers _VIVmag_ and our third-party service providers. You may always choose to not receive our marketing emails by following the instructions at the bottom of each email you receive from us. You may also change your preferences regarding the types of emails you receive from us by clicking [here](http://vivmag.com/contact-us/) to email us. 

**Links to Other Sites**

This Site contains links to third party websites that are provided for your convenience. _VIVmag_ does not endorse nor is it responsible for the privacy practices or the content or services of such websites. We recommend that you review the privacy policies and terms of use that govern those websites when you visit them.

**Children**

The Site is directed towards adults. _VIVmag_ does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 should not use this Site or submit information to us.

**Review and Correction**

We try to keep information about you accurate and current. If, however, you find errors or inaccuracies in your information, or if your contact information changes, please let us know by clicking [here](http://vivmag.com/contact-us/) to send us an e-mail, and we will update your information upon request.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the top of the Privacy Policy. For material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on our Site. We will not materially alter the use of your personally identifiable information without contacting you directly and seeking your affirmative consent.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please [click here](http://vivmag.com/contact-us/) to send us an e-mail.
